{
    "subject": "resource/Red_Rock_West",
    "predicate": "property/gross",
    "object": "2502551.0",
    "human_readable": "Red Rock West has a gross of 2502551.0.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7604111433029175,
            "question": "What was the gross revenue of Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6211047172546387,
            "question": "What was the total amount earned by Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5304055213928223,
            "question": "How much money did Red Rock West make?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4700767993927002,
            "question": "Can you tell me the box office earnings for Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.457561731338501,
            "question": "How much money did Red Rock West generate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42114266753196716,
            "question": "What is the financial success of Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3949981927871704,
            "question": "What is the revenue figure associated with the film Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37078624963760376,
            "question": "Is Red Rock West a financially successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2702866494655609,
            "question": "What is the financial performance of the film Red Rock West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20825789868831635,
            "question": "Give me the box office figures for Red Rock West."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Red Rock West has a gross of 2502551.0.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6564_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the financial performance of the film Red Rock West?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6564_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Red Rock West a financially successful film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6564_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the revenue figure associated with the film Red Rock West?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6564_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6564_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain:\n\nThe provided text discusses the critical reception, plot elements, and production details of the film \"Red Rock West\". However, it does not mention any financial information like its gross revenue.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention any information about the box office gross of the movie \"Red Rock West\". Therefore, we cannot confirm or deny a specific figure for its gross based on the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " Response: {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there is no mention of a gross revenue figure for Red Rock West in the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}